[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "This began at a home as I said, and ended at Santa Monica College, right?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Not at the moment.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Any more info on that?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, that's a good question, Piers.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Why do you believe you killed your parents?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "When I would watch \"The Matrix,\" I would see myself in that role.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Do you remember watching \"The Matrix\" repeatedly, watching these video games and the kind of effect it had on you?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, to put it bluntly, I -- I know that there's something wrong with me in -- in my head.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Do you believe now that that was the case?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "It impacted me a lot.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "How much was that playing on your mind, do you think, through this period leading up to what you did?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Yes, I do remember.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Do you remember where you got the gun and were you subjected to any kind of background check?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Actually, it wasn't.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "And was your intention, when you purchased the gun, to -- to murder your parents?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "They didn't know, really, what was going on.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "But did your adopted parents, do you think, have any real idea of what you were going through in your head?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well, no, my adopted parents, my father was -- he wasn't like that with me, but my mother, she would beat my sister and I a lot.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Because they never mistreated you, your adopted parents?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I had been listening to the song for about a year nonstop.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "What was going through your head as you heard that music?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "I believe so, especially on the young mind.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "But again, as with the violent video games, do you think that violent musical video and music can have a -- a profound and disturbing effect on people who may themselves be mentally unstable?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "That's a good question.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "And what then happened?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Actually, I had no emotion at all.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "As you were doing that, what was the sensation that you were experiencing?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, the things that went on that night, that it really reminded me -- it did remind me of \"The Matrix.\"", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Even at the moment that you'd realized you'd murdered both your parents, was there any kind of reality check or did you still believe that this was some weird, horrible, violent videogame that you were possibly enacting for real?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Well, I would say that, whenever I talk to anyone about this, I always tell them that I don't blame anyone but myself.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "What do you say to those people?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I agree.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "But do you think that system, the mental health system in America should have picked you up earlier?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "OOKE: Absolutely.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "When you've seen the mass shootings at places like Aurora, in the movie theater with James Holmes, and also with Adam Lanza at Sandy Hook, do you recognize, from everything that you've read about these two shooters similarities in the way that, perhaps, you were thinking at the time that you committed your atrocity?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Do you think that the easy availability of guns is also a big problem in America for disturbed young men in particular, like yourselves?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Well, first, I actually do believe that I will see them again.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "If you had the chance to speak to them again -- which you never will -- but if you did have the chance, what would you say to them?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "No, I'm not.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Are you -- are you now receiving any kind of treatment or medication for any mental health issues?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I thought he was extremely candid with you.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What did you make of it?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "The first thing you have to keep in mind is the number of people who play violent video games or watch movies like \"The Matrix\" and we don't see a lot of them killing anybody, let alone killing both their parents.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Are these just convenient excuses or is there real science to back up the fact that these can be a link to what these shooters do?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Well, 99.9 percent of those who watch the news about columbine or another shooting identify with the pain and suffering of the victims, and pray every day that a Columbine will not happen in their school.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "How much of that is a problem with these shootings where unstable young people who perhaps are disenfranchised from society want to make a stir for themselves, get in the headlines, become infamous?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "I get asked that question on the stand all the time in death penalty cases by prosecutors when I'm working for the defense.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "You can do it without being mentally unstable?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "I think here, the video game playing is a symptom, not a cause.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "And what was he doing with all of his time?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "I believe him.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "I mean, what do you think of the gun aspect of this?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Let me bring in James Fox here.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Is he being treated in prison?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Well, to some extent, we do know that people who are at the violent peak, late adolescence, early adulthood.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Do you believe that they can just grow out of this, even if they have a condition like schizophrenia?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Xavier, I'll start with you, do you believe him?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "About some things yes, some things no.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "James Fox?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "I think as he said it the way he sees it.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Cheryl Olson?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "I have a job now, this is my space to prepare myself to be better.", "docId": "130607pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "This little piggy goes to the market?", "qSentId": 493}]